Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost of Graduate Education, records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost of Graduate Education, records
1982-2004
SC1174
Stanford University. Office of the Vice Provost for Graduate Education.
3 Linear feet (2 cartons)
The records consist of administrative files including handbooks, TA manuals, and annual reports.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
This collection was transferred to Stanford University, Special Collections in October 2013.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
The Office of the Vice Provost for Graduate Education (VPGE) opened in January 2007 to further Stanford University’s commitment to excellence in graduate education. The mission of the Office of the VPGE is to provide academic leadership that accelerates Stanford’s efforts to enhance the quality of graduate education by fostering innovation. The Office of the VPGE collaborates across campus with the schools and programs that have primary responsibility for organizing and delivering Stanford's graduate education. The VPGE promotes and creates innovative pilot programs to advance diversity, encourage interdisciplinarity, and offer leadership and professional development opportunities for students.
Text from excerpeted from the Office of the Vice Provost for Graduate Education: (http://vpge.stanford.edu/about_us/index.html).
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files including handbooks, TA manuals, and annual reports.
Access Terms
Education--Study and teaching (Graduate)
Collection Contents
- Graduate Student Handbook, 2001 (Box 1)
- Code of Conduct, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Teaching Assistant Oversight Committee (TAOC), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- TA Guidelines, circa 1990s-200s (Box 1, Folder 3)
- TA-OK Task Force, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Graduate Studies Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Graduate Studies Annual Report: Activities of, 1989-1991 (Box 1)
- Graduate Studies Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
- Graduate Studies and Research Annual Report to the Provost, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Graduate Studies Report to the Provost, 1985-1986 (Box 2)